Guide to the Western Connecticut State University Photographs and Miscellanea RG 8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series III: Clippings, 55202
  - 1992, 55473
    - November 1992 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55475 (Box clippings_2, Folder 65)
      Nov 9, 1992: Western soccer in quarterfinals; Nov 23, 1992: Western football focuses on recruiting.
    - December 1992 Clippings (copies), 55474 (Box clippings_2, Folder 66)
      Dec 3,5, 1992: Kwanzaa, Western honors African holiday; Dec 3, 1992: Dr. Theresa J. Canada appointed prof. of Education and Education Psychology; Dec 23, 1992: Aids quilt may come to town.
  - 1993, 55456
    - January 1993 Clippings (copies), 55472 (Box clippings_2, Folder 67)
      Jan 11, 1993: Ancell students designed own brochure; Jan 22, 1993: $5,000 grant helps Western faculty, students in research.
    - January 1993 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55471 (Box clippings_2, Folder 68)
      Jan 31, 1993: Jody Rajacula's intensity drives Western women's basketball.
    - February 1993 Clippings (copies), 55470 (Box clippings_2, Folder 69)
      Feb 3-4,10,23-24, 1993: Wester+J427n celebrates Black History Month; Feb 4,6, 1993: Rita P. Wilson, Sr. V.P. Allstate Insurance Co., calls for diversity; Feb 9, 1993: President Franklyn Jenifer, Howard University President, calls for diversity; Feb 7, 1993: President Roach earns high marks on first report card; Feb 10-21,23, 1993: Charles Ives Center and Western clash over concerts; Feb 28, 1993: Western tackles charges that 'system' discriminates.
    - March 1993 Clippings (copies), 55469 (Box clippings_2, Folder 70)
      Mar 1, 1993: Western's minority presence soars; Mar 4, 1993: Ives Center dispute may be nearing resolution; Mar 5, 1993: AIDS memorial quilt coming in April; Mar 26,27, 1993: Ives Center schedule for 1993 season.
    - April 1993 Clippings (copies), 55468 (Box clippings_2, Folder 71)
      Apr 9, 1993: Western students confront racism; Apr 13, 1993: Autumn opening for O'Neill Center; Apr 15, 1993: Western candlelight vigil on racism, sexism and homophobia; Apr 18, 1993: Evelyn R. Pinney Obituary (wife of A. Searle Pinney); Apr 21, 1993: Western contemplates Rodney King verdict and racism; Apr 22, 1993: Gov. Lowell Weicker speaks out for religious freedom; Apr 25,27,29, 1993: AIDS quilt; Apr 27, 1993: Western professor John Dever and his class translate a job manual into Spanish for unemployed Latinos.
    - May 1993 Clippings (copies), 55467 (Box clippings_2, Folder 72)
      May 1, 1993: Western gets $13M for library; May 2, 1993: Ives Center executive director resigns; May 5, 1993: Consultant assesses racial tolerance at Western; May 9, 1993: Naughty by Nature headline WestFest '93; May 15, 1993: Ives Center picks Lisa P. Reiss as director; May 28, 1993: Students translate vocational workshop manual into Spanish.
    - May 1993 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55466 (Box clippings_2, Folder 73)
      May 5, 1993: Western recruits for soccer team; May 9, 1993: Scott Gentile making progress in the Montreal Expos' minor league system; May 30, 1993: Western football recruits 33 in-state players.
    - June 1933 Clippings (copies), 55465 (Box clippings_2, Folder 74)
      Jun 9, 1993: Western describe efforts to lure minorities; Jun 11, 1993: Minority employees, NAACP say racism entrenched at Western.
    - July 1993 Clippings (copies), 55464 (Box clippings_2, Folder 75)
      Jul 7, 1993: Council approves closure of part of Seventh Avenue; Jul 15, 1993: President Dallas K. Beal to resign; Jul 28, 1993: Dr. Mel Goldstein talks about the weather; Jul 30, 1993: WCSU race relations report overdue.
    - July 1993 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55463 (Box clippings_2, Folder 76)
      Jul 1, 1993: Western pitcher Mike Porzio signed by Cubs; Jul 30, 1993: Seven players Nutmeg Bowl are going to Western.
    - August 1993 Clippings (copies), 55462 (Box clippings_2, Folder 77)
      Aug 3, 1993: AIDS quilty display yields $1,755 which will be distributed to local AIDS charities; Aug 4, 1993: Higher Education: Western offers wide choice for future; Aug 17, 1993: Western race relations report withheld; Aug 20, 1993: Caleb L. Nichols, Western's first Director of Multicultural Affairs; Aug 20, 1993: Racial climate evaluated.
    - August 1993 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55461 (Box clippings_2, Folder 78)
      Aug 5, 1993: Local softball talent coming to Western; Aug 6, 1993: John Cervino and his four new assistant coaches.
    - September 1993 Clippings (copies), 55460 (Box clippings_2, Folder 79)
      Sep 1, 1993: Denise Hogan interview; Sep 19, 1993: Duke University's efforts to diversify fall short; Sep 26, 1993: News-Times Community Forum: James R. Roach "Planning Western's direction for the future."
    - October 1993 Clippings (copies), 55459 (Box clippings_2, Folder 80)
      Oct 6-7, 1993: Danbury Armory purchase; Oct 10, 1993: News-Times Community Forum: Caleb Nichols "Multiculturalism, demographics, diversity at issue;" Oct 12,14,25, 1993: NAACP and racial discrimination; Oct 15, 1993: Kevin Isaacs composes alma mater for Western; Oct 21, 1993: Western encouraged by accreditation progress; Oct 28, 1993: Ives Center and Western resolve lease dispute; Oct 28, 1993: Grease by Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Oct 29, 1993: $20,000 forgotten fund at Western promotes minority mentoring.
    - November 1993 Clippings (copies), 55458 (Box clippings_2, Folder 81)
      Nov 1, 1993: Elizabeth Sheff and race relations; Nov 2, 1993: Grease review; Nov 18, 1993: University Senate reviews hiring practices; Nov 23, 1993: Roy Bourgeois, priest-activist, still fighting.
    - December 1993 Clippings (copies), 55457 (Box clippings_2, Folder 82)
      Dec 1, 1993: Lynne Gilbert, new coordinator of Western's substance abuse prevention and education program; Dec 9, 1993: Western's diversity survey awaits analysis.
  - 1994, 55442
    - January 1994 Clippings (copies), 55455 (Box clippings_2, Folder 83)
      Jan 9, 1994: WCSU considers day care; Jan 3,16, 1994: O'Neill Center and White Street Garage.
    - February 1994 Clippings (copies), 55454 (Box clippings_2, Folder 84)
      Feb 4,7,9, 1994: Buildings: White Street property, fine arts center, Eastern Church, library work delayed; Feb 23, 1994: WCSU's Observatory to open in fall.
    - March 1994 Clippings (copies), 55453 (Box clippings_2, Folder 85)
      Mar 8, 1994: Scapinoby The Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Mar 13, 1994: Disabled students ask for easier access to classes; Mar 15,17, 1994: University Trustees resist restructuring; Mar 20, 1994: Gender bias; Mar 23, 1994: Al Pia, WCSU drama instructer, interview; Mar 23, 1994: WXCI tower proposal.
    - March 1994 Clippings (copies) - Sports, 55452 (Box clippings_2, Folder 86)
      Mar 13, 1994: Men's basketball team wins first Eastern College Athletic Conference title.
    - April 1994 Clippings (copies), 55451 (Box clippings_2, Folder 87)
      Apr 3,9, 1994: Danbury ice rink; Apr 21, 1994: Bruce Baylock leaving Western.
    - May 1994 Clippings (copies), 55450 (Box clippings_2, Folder 88)
      May 4, 1994: A Rootin Tootin Tall Tale special production given for students of the Roberts Avenue School; May 8, 1994: Study Skills Lab stirs controversy; May 12, 1994: Western's building projects delayed; May 13, 1994: Howie Mandel headlines WestFest '94; May 22, 1994: Professor Lionel Bascom says cronyism pervades Western; May 26, 1994: Goodall Wildlife Institute moving to Danbury.
    - June 1994 Clippings (copies), 55449 (Box clippings_2, Folder 89)
      Jun 9, 1994: William J. Cibes likely to take over State University System; Jun 16, 1994: Stephen Feldman leaves Florida post; Jun 20, 1994: Abrahim Bendardaf dismissal.
    - July 1994 Clippings (copies), 55448 (Box clippings_2, Folder 90)
      Jul 8,11, 1994: Botanists from Siberia and Mexico, and Western Tom Philbrick collaborate on aquatic plans in New England; Jul 15,31, 1994: Dr. Laurie Weinstein and students summer digging in Newtown's Upper Paugussett State Forest; Jul 31, 1994: Field House and poor management, huge cost overruns and lengthy delays.
    - August 1994 Clippings (copies), 55447 (Box clippings_2, Folder 91)
      Aug 3, 1994: Master Plan for White Street campus; Aug 3, 1994: Jane Goodall Institue headquarters in Danbury; Aug 3, 1994: Editorial: Wasteful (sports arena); Aug 14, 1994: Western's Affirmative Action Plan slammed by critics; Aug 24, 1994: Western's students try newsletter "Jet Gazette" (New York Jets); Aug 26,28, 1994: State panel probing bias claims at Western.
    - September 1994 Clippings (copies), 55446 (Box clippings_2, Folder 92)
      Sep 9, 1994: State Commission on Human Rights decides against discrimination inquiry at Western; Sep 28, 1994: Dean Joan Apple Lemoine leaving Western.
    - October 1994 Clippings (copies), 55445 (Box clippings_2, Folder 93)
      Oct 1, 1994: Prof. Philbrick and Lake Putnam; Oct 2, 1994: Astroturf at Western; Oct 19,28, 1994: CSUS President William Cibes; Oct 20,21,23,26, 1994: Western's affirmative action plan rejected by state's human rights agency.
    - November 1994 Clippings (copies), 55444 (Box clippings_2, Folder 94)
      Nov 5,16, 1994: Western librarian charged with child pornography; Nov 6,14, 1994: Field House does not meet all state building and fire codes; Nov 11, 1994: Hair by the Communications and Theatre Arts Department; Nov 13, 1994: Joyce Carol Oats at Western; Nov 14, 1994: Prof. Frank Dye and nature preserve on the west side campus; Nov 20, 1994: News-Times Community Forum: Sara T. DeLoughy, Ancell School, "Region must develop long-term vision of job growth;" Nov 23,26, 1994: Western and State make 1-year deal (State won't call for hiring freeze if school shows solid commitment to minorities).
    - December 1994 Clippings (copies), 55443 (Box clippings_2, Folder 95)
      Dec 4, 1994: Western's choice of builder for domitory questioned; Western tries again on Affirmative Action Plan; Dec 8, 1994: Western's racial climate; Dec 13,16, 1994: A World Wide Holidayby The Communications and Theatre Arts Department.
  - 1997, 55423
    - Arts and Sciences Meet the Press, 1996-1997 (Box clippings_2, Folder 95.5)
    - January 1997 Clippings (copies), 55441 (Box clippings_2, Folder 96)
      Jan 8, 1997: Ancell School and Direct Marketing and Technology classes; Jan 17, 1997: Ancell School Business Symposium; Jan 30, 1997: Building problems persist at Western.
    - January 1997 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55440 (Box clippings_2, Folder 97)
      Jan 19, 1997: The future of Division III NCAA.
    - February 1997 Clippings (originals), 55439 (Box clippings_2, Folder 98)
      Feb 2, 1997: Editorial: Memorial Hall and building delays; Feb 5, 1997: Black History Month exhibition and discussion "Constitutional Issues: Yesterday & Today;" Feb 14, 1997: School cuts raise concerns at Western; Feb 18, 1997: Gov. Rowland says "CSU system classic example of waste and redundancy;" Feb 18, 1997: Alumni Hall; Feb 26, 1997: Xiaodi Wang, Western math professor recreates math tests for junior and high school students.
    - March 1997 Clippings (originals), 55438 (Box clippings_2, Folder 99)
      Mar ? 1997: Dr. Abubaker Saad interview; Mar 7,12, 1997: Author Andrea Dworkin to speak at Western; Mar 7, 1997: Jane Goodall at the federal prison in Danbury; Mar 11, 1997: Wetlands deal lets dorm project proceed on westside campus; Mar ?, 1997: News-Times Community Forum: Dr. James R. Roach "Western looks to challenges of a new century;" Mar 20, 1997: Women's History Month event: Roe vs. Wade. Speakers Phyllis Schlafly and Sarah Weddington; Mar 26, 1997: John Leopold discusses book by Daniel Jonah Goldhagen "Hitler's Willing Executioners--Ordinary Germans and the Holocaust."
    - March 1997 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55437 (Box clippings_2, Folder 100)
      Mar 9, 1997: Women's basketball team wins second round in Division III NCAA tournament.
    - April 1997 Clippings (originals), 55436 (Box clippings_2, Folder 101)
      Apr 15, 1997: State budget cuts devastating to CSUS, especially Western; Apr 19, 1997: Second sexual harassment complain against Prof. Sal Trapani dismissed by WCSU; Apr 25-26, 1997: Annual Jazz Festival and The Joe Lovano Quartet.
    - May 1997 Clippings (originals), 55435 (Box clippings_2, Folder 102)
      May, 1997: Western Connecticut State University and the Community supplement; May 7, 1997: Truman Warner dies; May 16, 1997: Memorial Hall renovation to restart; May 16, 1997: WCSU police officers patrol campus on new electric bicyles; May 24, 1997: Dr. Melvin Goldstein receives second President's Medal bestowed by Western; May 30, 1997: Database from Ancell tracks local economic trends.
    - June 1997 Clippings (originals), 55434 (Box clippings_2, Folder 103)
      Jun 5, 1997: Students awaiting House vote to increase number of student reps to sit on the BOT; Jun 7, 1997: Eugene Buccini interim Academic Affairs VP; Jun 10, 1997: Andrea Pack, a junion at Western, receives Hord Foundation scholarship; Jun 11, 1997: Echo wins top press honors; Jun 17, 1997: Western's Catherine A. Johnston and Juel Bynoe Reid receive Henry Barnard Awards.
    - July 1997 Clippings (originals), 55433 (Box clippings_2, Folder 104)
      Jul 15, 1997: Western adds criminal justice master's; Jul 27, 1997: Truman Warner leaves paper "monument" for scholars; Jul/Aug, 1997: Danbury/Housatonic Valley Business Digest, "The Ancell School of Business" profile.
    - August 1997 Clippings (originals), 55432 (Box clippings_2, Folder 105)
      Aug 4, 1997: News Times Thumbs Up to Herb Janick and Jim Pegolotti re Truman Warner papers; Aug 5, 1997: New alliance between WCSU and Naugatuck Valley Community and Technical College; Aug 6, 1997: Western offers new U.S. Studies curriculum; Western, Goodall Institue start a cooperative venture; New graduate program in criminal justice at Western; Professional Studies at Western attract 1,000 students; Freshman class largest since 1970s; Western's theater group travels to Edinburgh Festival; Edinburgh Festival Newspaper Three Weeks critiques WCSU's productions: A Trip to the Farm, and Ibsen's Enemy of the People.
    - September 1997 Clippings (originals), 55431 (Box clippings_2, Folder 106)
      Sep 5, 1997: Ted Hines interview; Sep 9, 1997: Ribbon cutting and opening of Western's Child Care Center; Sep 10, 1997: Goodall Institute moving to D.C.; Sep 16, 1997: Tiger-TV (Ridgefield HS) interviews Jane Goodall; Sep 16, 1997: City disburses grand to day care centers; Sept.19, 1997: WCSU Child Care Center opens.
    - October 1997 Clippings (originals), 55430 (Box clippings_2, Folder 107)
      Oct ?, 1997: Rabbi Malino honored for community service; Oct 4, 1997: Sputnik; 40 years later; Oct 7-8, 1997: Martin Margulies, law professor at Quinnipiac College School of Law lecture "Power and the First Amendment" Gino Arconti Lecture Series; Oct 17, 1997: Weather forecasting team at Western is Number 1 again; Oct 23, 1997: Dr. Mel celebrates 52nd birthday; Oct 30, 1997: State legislature lifts campus ban against military recruiters.
    - November 1997 Clippings (originals), 55429 (Box clippings_2, Folder 108)
      Nov 1,13, 1997: Arthur Miller's A View from the Bridge by the Department of Communications and Theatre Arts; Nov 11, 1997: Echo: Profile of Dr. Eugene Buccini; Nov 21, 1997: Western student Hidenobu Hara wins sculpture award; Nov 22, 1997: Western officials hope students will study in China.
    - November 1997 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55428 (Box clippings_2, Folder 109)
      Nov 5,7, 1997: Western's defensive back Bobby McClain named to the 1997 American Football Coaches Association's Good Works teams; Nov 25-26, 1997: Jody Rajcula profile and records 300th win.
    - December 1997 Clippings (originals), 55427 (Box clippings_2, Folder 110)
      Dec 2, 1997: Planets dot the night sky; Dec 7, 1997: Speaker Michele James, president of the National Coalition of 100 Black Women talk about "Dreams: The seed for success."
    - December 1997 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55426 (Box clippings_2, Folder 111)
      Dec 4, 1997: Western soccer coach Joe Mingachos named coach of the year in the Metro Region; Dec 7, 1997: Western's women's basketball full-court press wins against Plymouth State.
    - December 1997 Clippings (originals), 55425 (Box clippings_2, Folder 112)
      Dec 16, 1997: Koryoe Anim-Wright new Public Relations Director for Westerm; Dec 16,19, 1997: A. Searle Pinney honored as city's top entrepreneur; Dec 18, 1997: Holiday dorm closing poses problem for 26 international students; Dec 19, 1997: Meserve Memorial Fund will save Truman Warner's papers; Dec 21, 1997: Armistad comes to life with discovery of old newspaper; Dec 26, 1997: University faculty gave a vote no confidence in hasty efforts to fill posts; Dec 30, 1997: Prof. Charles Mullaney interview.
    - December 1997 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55424 (Box clippings_2, Folder 113)
      Dec 11, 1997: Kevin Reed, defensive end, named to the Hewlett-Packard Division III All-American second team for second, straight season; Dec 14, 1997: Former student, Steve Kaplanis coach at Immaculate High, interview; Dec 17, 1997: Women's basketball captain Stacey Williams; Dec 30, 1997: Women's basketball team wins Hoopla title.
    - October-November 1997 Clippings digest (1 issue) (Box Clippings Digest 1, Item 4)
  - 1998, 55379
    - January 1998 Clippings (originals), 55402 (Box clippings_2, Folder 114)
      Jan 3, 1998: Nathan Ancell selling off art collection; Jan 6, 1999: Martin Moore, past pres.SGA and CSUS student trustee, youngest Republican councilman in Danbury Common Council; Jan 7, 1998: Upgraded Ancell faculty and classroom computers; Jan 9, 1998: New 425-bed dormitory to be named in honor of Searle Pinney; Jan 15, 1998: Lessons of Armistad; Jan 29, 1998: WCSU receives $16.6M for Haas Library renovation and addition.
    - January 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55401 (Box clippings_2, Folder 115)
      Jan 10, 1998: Women's basketball Kim Camella interview; Jan 29, 1998: Football defensive end Kevin Reed.
    - February 1998 Clippings (originals), 55400 (Box clippings_2, Folder 116)
      Feb 12, 1998: State gives WCSU $1M to buy 50 acres on the Westside Campus; Feb 12, 1998: Joan Harrison, acting Director of Student Life, loses bid to apply for job; Feb 15, 1998: Western students study Goodall African films; Feb 15, 1998: Kenneth Young, prof. emeritus of history, has written The General's General, a biography of Gen Arthur MacArthur; Feb 24, 1998: Ruth Haas remembered in Scott-Fanton Museum exhibit.
    - February 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55399 (Box clippings_2, Folder 117)
      Feb 24, 1998: Men's and women's basketball LEC playoffs.
    - March 1998 Clippings (originals), 55398 (Box clippings_2, Folder 118-119)
      March, 1998: Dr. Mel Goldstein's "Weatherwords" appears daily in March; Mar 3, 1998: Abubaker Saad on Iraq; Mar 8, 1998: Fiddler on the Roof by the Communications & Theatre Arts Department; Mar 15, 1998: News-Times Community Forum: Charles P. Mullaney; Mar 15, 1998: "Dr. Mel Goldstein, The wise man of the weather"; Mar 15,20, 1998: Robert Alberetti and family to exhibit artwork at the Silo Gallery; Mar 22, 1998: Dr. Mel recovering from cancer; Mar 27, 1998: Haas library project ahead of schedule; Mar 27,31, 1998: Clothesline Project "Bearing Witness to Violence Against Women."
    - March 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55397 (Box clippings_2, Folder 120)
      Mar 11, 1998: Women's basketball: Amy Matthews; Mar 25, 1998: Four joining Connecticut Women's Basketball Hall of Fame (Bonnie Foley, Lynn Spagnesi, Trish Neary, and Pat Mascia).
    - March 1998 Clippings (originals), 55396 (Box clippings_2, Folder 121)
      March 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web Edition.
    - April 1998 Clippings (originals), 55395 (Box clippings_2, Folder 122-125)
      April, 1998: Dr. Mel Goldstein's "Weatherwords" appears daily in April; Apr 1,9, 1998: WCSU's Darla Shaw featured in a Learning/Discovery Channel program "Amazing People;" Apr 14, 1998: Prof. Laurie Weinstein's books Wives & Warriors and Gender Camouflage: Women and the U.S. Military; Apr 19, 1998: Students and marijuana; Apr 24,29, 1998: Jane Goodall speaks out on saving the world for future generations.
    - April 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55394 (Box clippings_2, Folder 126)
      April, 1998: Men and women's softball; Apr 13, 1998: Women's soccer team: Stacy Havener; Apr 15, 1998: Kevin Reed, defensive end, awaits NFL draft; Apr 30, 1998: Former student Trish Neary to be inducted into the Connecticut Women's Basketball Hall of Fame.
    - April 1998 Clippings (originals), 55393 (Box clippings_2, Folder 127)
      April 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web Edition.
    - May 1998 Clippings (originals), 55392 (Box clippings_3, Folder 1-2)
      May, 1998: Dr. Mel Goldstein's "Weatherwords" appears daily in May; May 1,4, 1998: WCSU student Hillary Tyler's "Hope Chest" wins New Playwrights Competition; May 7,8,12, 1998: Opening of student center and groundbreaking for addition to Haas Library; May7,8,11, 1998: Speaker Millard Fuller, founder and president of Habitat for Humanity International, celebrates 20th anniversary of the college's Christian Ministry; May 12, 1998: Dallas K. Beal to speak at commencement; May 20, 1998: Gene Buccini named Vice President of Academic Affairs; May 27, 1998: Westside Nature Preserve.
    - May 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55391 (Box clippings_3, Folder 3)
      May 9, 1998: Western softball team to host ECAC tournament; May 20, 1998: Kevin Reed to play indoor football.
    - May 1998 Clippings (originals), 55390 (Box clippings_3, Folder 4)
      May 3-27, 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web Edition.
    - June 1998 Clippings (originals), 55389 (Box clippings_3, Folder 5)
      Jun 17, 1998: Laurie Weinstein instructs student Russ Bennett digs for Indian artifacts; Jun 21, 1998: Daryle Dennis, balancing career/young children/community activism; Jun 29, 1998: Harambee finds home at armory.
    - June 1998 Clippings (originals), 55388 (Box clippings_3, Folder 6)
      June 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web.
    - August 1998 Clippings (originals), 55387 (Box clippings_3, Folder 7)
      Aug 1, 1998: Bond Commission approves $400,000 for WCSU to buy communications and laboratory equipment.
    - September 1998 Clippings (originals), 55386 (Box clippings_3, Folder 8)
      Sep 6, 1998: Ten year old Cassandra Stevenson's first day as freshman at WCSU; Sep 13, 1998: Rick Asselta's summer in Tanzania; Sep 20, 1998: Growth spurt at WCSU; Sep 29, 1998: Mia Farrow discusses her children, her beliefs for WCSU class.
    - September 1998 Clippings (originals), 55385 (Box clippings_3, Folder 9)
      Sep 29, 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web Edition.
    - October 1998 Clippings (originals), 55384 (Box clippings_3, Folder 10)
      Oct 16, 1998: Averell Manes, Director of Conflict Resolution/Ancell School; Oct 31, 1998: Ancell holds first conference on resolving conflict in the workplace.
    - November 1998 Clippings (originals), 55383 (Box clippings_3, Folder 11)
      Nov 11, 1998: Prof. Peter Lyons shares stories of his time working in Ulan Bator, the capital of Mongolia; Nov 20, 1998: Joe Torre speaks at WCSU.
    - November 1998 Clippings (originals) - Sports, 55382 (Box clippings_3, Folder 12)
      Nov 11, 1998: Men's soccer team in first round of NCAA Division III tournament.
    - November 1998 Clippings (originals), 55381 (Box clippings_3, Folder 13)
      November 1998: Burrell's World Wide Web.
    - December 1998 Clippings (originals), 55380 (Box clippings_3, Folder 14)